<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<RelativeLayout xmlns:android="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res/android"
    android:layout_width="match_parent" android:layout_height="match_parent">

    <LinearLayout
        android:layout_width="match_parent"
        android:layout_height="match_parent"
        android:layout_alignParentTop="true"
        android:layout_centerHorizontal="true"
        android:orientation="horizontal">

        <ScrollView
            android:layout_width="match_parent"
            android:layout_height="match_parent">

            <LinearLayout
                android:layout_width="match_parent"
                android:layout_height="wrap_content"
                android:orientation="vertical" >

                <TextView
                    android:id="@+id/textView2"
                    android:layout_width="match_parent"
                    android:layout_height="wrap_content"
                    android:layout_alignParentBottom="true"
                    android:layout_alignParentEnd="true"
                    android:layout_alignParentTop="true"
                    android:text="The two pegs for each player are used to indicate the score in the previous turn and the score of the current turn. The first to accumulate 121 points wins. This often occurs in the middle of a deal; the game then ends immediately. The dealer gets the advantage of the crib; however, the non-dealer(s) immediately gets 3 points. The player who did not deal cuts the deck to determine the top card. Then, the dealer should flip it over. Both players will use this card, called the &quot;cut,&quot; as a wild fifth card to count points at the end of the round. Players alternate laying cards down. As they play each card, they call out the value of the total. Face cards have a value of 10; all others are worth their numeric value. Aces are always only worth 1 point. Suits do not matter in this round; only numeric values. Play stops at 31 (or when no one can lay down a card).  Make pairs, runs, and other combinations to score points. While you're laying cards and thinking about not going over 31, use what your opponent(s) is laying to your advantage. You get extra points for pairs, runs, and certain numbers. As you score, move your peg around the board. If either player reaches 15 points exactly, this earns him 2 points. Points are also earned and pegged for pairs (and triplets, etc.). For example, player 1 lays down a 7 and Player 2 immediately follows with another 7, which would earn him 2 points. If Player 1 then lays down a third 7, he earns 6 points. The fourth seven would be worth 12 points. (Note: if Player 2 is not able to lay down any other card without exceeding 31, and Player 1 has the fourth seven, he can lay it down and earn the 12 points.). Sequences also score points. They must be consecutive cards, but not necessarily in order. For example: The first player plays a 4, second player plays a 6. If the first player now plays a 5 he would score three points for completing a run of 3. If the second player now plays a 3 or a 7 he would then score 4 points for making a run of 4.  After &quot;31&quot; (or as close as possible in the hand), the person laying down the last card takes a point for having the final card. If the last card makes exactly 31, the player gets 1 additional point. At this point, he says &quot;Go.&quot; If the other player can still lay down another card without exceeding 31, he must do so for as many times as necessary. Once he lays down as many cards as he can without going over 31, he says &quot;Go&quot; and earns 1 point. However, if the total he ends up with is exactly 31, he earns 2 points. It is 1 point per &quot;Go,&quot; not 1 point per card able to be laid down without exceeding 31. If you can lay 1 card without exceeding 31, you get 1 point; if you can lay 3 cards without exceeding 31, you still get 1 point. This player can also get extra points for runs and the like during this time. Once all cards have been played, it is time to count them up. The person to count first is the non-dealer(s), then the dealer, then the crib. Your hand consists of the four cards you played, plus the cut card. This is why you kept them in separate piles! If you are the dealer, count your original hand and the crib separately. You score one point if you hold the Jack of the suit that was cut. Pairs, triples and quadruples count -- 2, 6 and 12 points, respectively. Sequences (e.g. 6-7-8) do not have to be the same suit, and count as 1 point per card. They must consist of at least three cards. Any combination of cards that add up to 15 counts as 2 points (even if it took all five cards to do it). You may use a card more than once in different combinations. A flush (all four cards are the same suit) is worth 4 points. The cut cannot give you a flush. It gives a fifth point if it extends a 4 card flush to a 5 card flush, but 3 spades and a heart don't score flush points if you cut a spade. (When counting the crib, only 5 card flushes score.) If all four cards in the crib are the same suit, no points can be taken unless the fifth card is also that same suit. Then 5 points are pegged." />
            </LinearLayout>
        </ScrollView>
    </LinearLayout>

</RelativeLayout>